hello yeah yeah Natty legs the people
want another performance oh God you got
to give it to them you got to give them
what they want I got to get my ready on
you better to get out there Natty legs
I got a tonight at the comedy
joint IIT the stage get my on point
I get my muscles loose with that Jacuzzi
fog then I get a portrait painted of me
and my dog I sit for a portrait of me
and mayor cutie then I get it airbrushed
on my booty then they paint it on a cake
I only take one bite those starving
kids got to keep my Stitch tight drink
40 cups of Throat Coat while I cooking
my quail and after all that I have my
money detail got to have your cream
steam there's germs on money and when
it's all wrinkled got to fluff and fold
honey got to take another bath in
prehistoric mud back back to my room
where I get new blood the only blood
that works for me is Blue
Blood
Mig myyl while I with my G and my
jewelry designo right before the I geted
and W then I go to the network it's time
to get
[Music]
paid I elegant that's what I be so damn
fancy got a diamond puss the diamond
the diamond
py no no no no no no Natasha the budget
for your special is out of control we've
got to keep this thing simple look I can
show you market research that proves
people do not want to see effort uh-uh I
didn't get into this business to read
okay then I'll summarize it for you okay
specials aren't special anymore and
you're making yours way too special
you're spending too much money I haven't
even finished my intro yet I know I can
still hear the music this is the perfect
time to drain it in have you seen these
Louis CK specials he literally gets off
the bus he wipes mustard off his shirt
he does the show in a t-shirt that's a
producer's dream I can get you a t-shirt
that's what people want no frills okay
I'll think about it thought about it
hell no okay it's really annoying when
you talk in Tempo to the music okay cuz
it sounds like you're rapping and I'm
sorry but you cannot call the special
Diamond but I had a Polish for the
show okay it looks amazing but we have
got to stop spending
money shut the hell up Mr wearing a suit
man table
flip don't flip my don't flip the table
it's glass please thank you this
patriarchal society name of this special
still be Diamond that was a waste
of my time my show starts in 10 and I
still got a whole bunch of air in I got
business I need forever stamps
there such a good value got me super AMP
one more thing I need to address an
unfortunate byproduct up saying yes down
to the clinic I'm a superstar all those
know who I are cuz I have a
career I ain't having babies the price
of two babies equals five Mercedes I
need another abortion so I pay the fee
if I get two more 61's free do you want
to use this one today no that's okay
I'll pay while they get the baby
they massage my legs while get the baby
I steak and eggs then I have the wait to
bring a light dessert Bye Bye Baby
Mama's eating Shar I eat steak and eggs
and lamb and ham post my meal and
abortion all on Instagram I get away
with this y'all cuz I'm famous and
Wealthy always got time for a selfie I
got to finish this get my ass to
the club I'mma do my show high on
abortion drug I feel 10 lb lighter even
with the stink and now my body's back to
it's PR off wa it takes a lot of
Maintenance to keep all this juicy and
that's how I keep this diamond py now
I'm ready for my show I call it what I
want they want this shiny from
China to Vermont Ben and Jerry a couple
of wussies binge on a of diamond
py diamond
py diamond py iant that's what I be so
damn fancy got a diamond pose Diamond
POS
[Music]
ladies and Gentlemen please welcome
Natasha
[Applause]
[Music]
leero